# VITALII NAUMENKO

- +380 96 080 3451
- ✓ naumenko.vitalii@ukr.net
- in Vitalii Naumenko
- **Q** Kyiv, Ukraine

### profile

### Front End Developer

Front End Developer with 5+ years of experience executing with plethora diverse skills. Enjoy working closely with team members to ensure workloads are effectively. With a passion for both personal growth and for software development. Ready to apply my passion for coding to a talented developers team to develop quality solutions.

### education

#### **Information Security**

Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics

Sep 2008 - Jul 2011

### skills

- · HTML
- CSS/Preprocessor CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React.js
- GraphQLTWIG
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap

## languages

Ukrainian [ native ]
English [ intermediate ]

### work experience

#### **Easy Pay**

Kyiv, Ukraine Feb 2022 - May 2024

#### **Front End Developer**

- Worked with product and back-end teams to create web product.
- Architected product tours with React for a new feature that improved customer.
- Migrated a multi-page user experience into a single page app which improved customer engagement.

#### **NDA**

Kyiv, Ukraine Jun 2020 - Nov 2021

#### **Front End Developer**

- Development and implementation of new modules and support current functionality.
- Partnered with data science to develop the front-end for a product recommendation engine that increased user time on page.

#### NDA

Kyiv, Ukraine Apr 2018 - Oct 2019

#### **Front End Developer**

- Designing and developing features to meet customer requirements and business goals.
- Building high quality and highly reliable software to meet the needs of the product owners.
- Writing clean, elegant, and reusable code that solves complex problems.

#### WD & SS

Kyiv, Ukraine Jun 2017 - Apr 2018

#### **Front End Developer**

- Developing websites for internal project design management.
- Identified and implemented dynamic web solutions in line with company standards and best practices.